[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "It's all going to plan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "You know, when the vote started getting counted we knew pretty quickly we have -- you know, we have a fairly sophisticated model.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "Were you pleased about the level of the turnout?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "If you were putting your strategist's hat on and looking at their campaign, where do you think they really, in the end, lost it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "But I think the problem for the Republican Party is that the center of gravity has shifted so far to the right that they're way out of the mainstream.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "But how much of the responsibility lies with him, with Speaker Boehner, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "Well, I think that he certainly bears some -- people want cooperation on both sides.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Boehner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "Are you hoping you're going to get the kind of economic security if not prosperity in this term that will allow you to do perhaps the things Barack Obama, when you sailed in on hope and change, hoped he could do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "Well, Piers, I do believe the economy is improving, but I want to challenge a bit of your premise because one of the reasons the economy is improving is because this president was brave.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "One is, I understand that the first person the president called after knowing that he won was Bill Clinton, is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bill Clinton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "Does he feel a big debt of gratitude to him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "Well, there's no question about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "Are you a relieved man this morning?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "Well, I know this has the subject of a lot of discussion.", "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["this morning"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "What was the mood like as victory became a reality?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "Well, it was a very exciting night.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "And how is your father about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "He was -- he was, you know, over the moon.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David Axelrod", "Jack Lew"]}, "docId": "121107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "What is the strategy here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "Well, you know, I'm going to leave the strategy, obviously, to David Axelrod and to the president and his staff, and his chief of staff, Jack Lew, and my father.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "What's your father's plan now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "His plan is to get to work.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "He must be feeling pretty proud, isn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "Well, I think he is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "The former CEO of G.E. joins me now to talk about the election, the fallout and -- well, what happened to your mate, Mitt Romney?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "CC", ":", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "Well, he didn't get it done.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["G.E."], "PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "You know, I -- he didn't get the minorities, he didn't get the young women.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "But, I mean, look, the Republicans have got to be less intransigent, too, haven't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNPS", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "Would he had been bolder and braver, perhaps most successful had he gone for Marco Rubio or Condoleezza Rice, somebody a bit different from Paul Ryan who looked like a younger version of Mitt Romney?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "RB", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "You know, that's the second guessing, and I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marco Rubio", "Condoleezza Rice", "Paul Ryan", "Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marco Rubio"]}, "docId": "121107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "But who's the kinder of person?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "Well, Marco Rubio is a very appealing guy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "Christie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "-- changing demographics.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Mother Nature"]}, "docId": "121107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "Tell me what it's like where you are, but also what is your view of the repeated storms we're seeing at the moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "It is Mother Nature's one-two punch.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "When you woke up this morning, what were the things that went through your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "A lot of it was just relief.", "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["this morning"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["end of the day"]}, "docId": "121107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "What do you want to see him really going harder at?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "JJR", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "Look, at the end of the day, we know what our problems are.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "What do you put the blame down to for the loss of support amongst women?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "TO", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "Well, the margin was pretty typically for a successfully elected incumbent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "Was it number four?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Hang on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}, "docId": "121107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "Cecile?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "Look, I think it was so clear last night.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "Where is that in the exit polls?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "Let's agree on one thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kelly Anne"]}, "docId": "121107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "Can I see that quote please?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "I was actually on with you, Kelly Anne, on a panel where you said women didn't care about women's health issues.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "Is he capable of delivering the old American dream now in a second term?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul Ryan"]}, "docId": "121107pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "Should he have gone for a braver pick, a Marco Rubio, a Condoleezza Rice?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "I don't know that Paul Ryan hurt him that much, because I think, at the end of the day, people don't vote for the vice president.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Condoleezza Rice"], "PERSON": ["Marco Rubio"]}}]